Divinity Original Sin 2 is a game made by Belgians
That information is not important to the video, I just thought you should know
It's a fantasy RPG with seven endings
And the hardest ending to get is the pacifist ending, when you don't kill a single person.
It's hard because people in Divinity are more fragile than eggshells
Today I'm gonna show you how to not kill anyone
First create a character, obviously I want a skeleton
Being made out of bone makes them immune to arrows and heart disease
But I can't pick him, because it is just too spooky
I'm making a dwarf, named Dwarf
His parents were nationalists (heil Gimli)
Finally tags for my backround
Noble, barbarian... ehh, how about all of them?
The game's backstory is that they capture people with magic bars and send them to a fort
The main character has a magic bar
We wake up on a ship with a feeling of déjà vu
Why am I level 30 with like every upgrade?
That's not right, and what's going on here?
She's investigating a murder
I think you are a bit late if there is no meat left
I don't think I can solve this mystery without killing anyone
I'll talk to her
No don't shoot!
Damn it, I just wanted to chat
Ah, now the whole ship is in chaos
So, we are not up to a great start, but this is just a tutorial level
I don't think it counts
See, the ship gets ripped up by a giant fish. They would have died anyways
And we gets saved by God
We made it to the fort with no kills
Oh no, that frog is about to die!
Does that count as my kill because I did not stop it? (Yes you psycho!)
[Manly noises]
I have to try!
Uh oh
Eh, not the tutorial anymore...
But you can't prove these kills if there were no witnesses [*Sighs* Guess I will have to report this then]
Woah, everyone here died of mysterious circumstances
We need to get out of this fort
Oh yeah, there is no one guarding the exit
We made it out
Be not frightened of me!
Ah, that was self defence
He was coming straight for me!
To get off this island I need to talk with people at the shrine of Madia
Here everyone is sad for some reason
Maybe we can help them out
I killed everyone, I don't know how this happened!
I was trying to buy a health potion, it was too expensive. Then I set fire...
Ok, now I remember how it happened
Can't pretend this time
The only thing that can forgive me now is the dwarf God
Dwarf, I forgive you for killing seven thousand people
What?! I killed thirty at most
Yeah, but some of them where farmers. And you know... consequences
Heh
[The awkard silence of your first date]
How do I get off this island now?
Um, a boat
New goal, steal a boat
Maybe I can summon a small worm to sneak past them and steal a ship for me
Forgot I was max level
At least I'm not killing anyone
Now how do I get on a boat?
A half demon named "M'lady" shows up to help the God friends
There was supposed to be six more of us, but they aren't here and no one knows why
Then our boat is attacked and I am super overpowered for some reason
I can probably take on the final boss right now and end the game with 0 kills
No don't teleport the ship, she is almost dead
Yeah, I'm gonna kill M'lady
Welcome to Tokyo driftwood
I am supposed to find a mentor, but she's not here
She is... Yeah, can't show that
*sighs* Why am I wearing my Toy Story hat?
I found a note on her
I'm supposed to combine a bunch of stuff and set fire to it
Then sniffing these deadly toxins will allow us speak to God
Just like real life
Wow, you really suck at this
Maybe you can grow more empathy if you could talk to the dead
We can now talk to ghost
Using it-
God damnit!
I hate this (text creation)!
I hate you all!
(-The writer of this text)
I'm killing everyone and declaim myself God in this world!
[Kilian on a murder spree]
So now everyone is dead and I can't progress
Still want an ending
Kilian, weren't you chosen by the actual God. Can't he help you?
Yes, the problem with that...
Duna, I have a problem
Oh, I get it
What?
I see what's happening here
No, you're a dead God!
When I said everyone dead I meant everyone dead
Except one
There's supposed to be a djinn here, but he could be anywhere
In that rock, in that bush, in that smoking lamp
Oh
Ah, the mass murdering Dwarf
Yeah, you're a dead djinn
No don't, I can make your wish come true and resurrect everyone
I don't think that would work
I wish to go back, for none of this to have happened
I can do that too
We wake up on a ship with a feeling of déjà vu
Why am I level thirty with every upgrade?
That's not correct
And what's going on here?
We're off to a bad start
What an aggresive guy
Damn it! Everyone has to die!
Welcome back!
We wake up on a ship with a feeling of do over
Why am I...
That was a close one...
Death to everyone!
You haven't grown a centimeter
[Kilian talking in Swedish]
[Evil laughter]
[The most boring boss battle I've ever seen]
Eh, I'll find a faster way
[Rickedy Roadster :D]